[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stan Smith is married to Francine and is the father of Hayley and Steve in this popular cartoon.", "correct_answer": "American Dad!", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fairly Odd Parents", "All in the Family", "The Simpson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Ruthenium?", "correct_answer": "Ru", "incorrect_answers": ["R", "Rh", "Rt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Talladega Nights, Ricky Bobby is a member of what team?", "correct_answer": "Dennit Racing", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Childress Racing", "Milton and Larry", "Billybob Racing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This low-carb vegetable was first seen along Atlantic coasts of Europe. Its in the same group as cauliflower, broccoli, kale, collards, kohlrabi, and Brussels sprouts.", "correct_answer": "Cabbage", "incorrect_answers": ["Lettuce", "Dill", "Carrot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you multiply any six consecutive whole numbers the product will be divisible by 8.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Hall of Fame is located in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma ?", "correct_answer": "Cowboy Hall of Fame", "incorrect_answers": ["Sooner Hall of Fame", "College Football hall of Fame", "Oil Industry Hall of Fame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the Henry Ford museum located?", "correct_answer": "Greenfield Village", "incorrect_answers": ["Detroit", "Taos", "Dearborn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following battles was not fought during World War Two?", "correct_answer": "Battle of Jutland", "incorrect_answers": ["Battle of Guadalcanal", "Battle of Kursk", "Battle of Tobruk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gollum was a marvel of computer graphics in The Lord of the Rings. What actor gave Gollum his movements?", "correct_answer": "Andy Serkis", "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Deezen", "Fat Joe", "Savion Glover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chef Jeff Smith of the Frugal Gourmet fame was removed from his TV show amid accusations of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "sexual harrasment", "incorrect_answers": ["plagiarism", "unsanitary kitchen practices", "low ratings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The government of this country condemned the 1997 movie Seven Years in Tibet and the director and the starring actors were banned from ever visiting the country.", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "North Korea", "Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tandoori Chicken is a meal named after the oven in which it is cooked - a small clay oven using a wood fire.", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "Thailand", "Siam"]}]